David Conner



> Status: Fullstack JS Engineer, M.Sc. Digital Media, Consultant

> Fields: Project Management, Software Develop-

ment, Consulting

Education

2015 / 07 - University of Bremen

Graduated as M.Sc. Digital Media

- Master Thesis: Semi Automated Scoring in Technology Based Assessment
- Developed and evaluated an algorithm for semi automated scoring of spreadsheet data

2012 - 2013 - University of Bremer

Master Project - PrIMA

- ➤ Co-Invented a touch table application for medical support, co-developed software (Java)
- Formed a scrum team, mainted project dev server (Debian), surveyed target audience

2012 - 2015 - University of Bremen

Master Studies Digital Media

- Inter-cultural classes in English, covering special topics in computer science and design
- Professionalized in research methods, software development and e-assessment

2009 - 2010 - University of Melbourne

Semester Abroad

- Mastered six months of study and trans-cultural experience in Melbourne, Australia
- Finished machine programming, information visualization, professional essay writing

2007 - 2012 - University of Bremen

Bachelor Studies Digital Media

- > Fundamentals in Computer Science
- ▶ Bachelor thesis focused on experimental redesign of the keyboard to support functional illiterates.

Summary

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino

Currently I develop and evaluate the next generation learning management system with Meteor based on an extensive nursing curriculum for healthcare education. I also love fitness, martial arts, videogames, news and Sci-Fi series.

Tech: Meteor, Javascript, Bootstrap, Mongodb, Git,

Webstorm, Sourcetree, Terminal

Loves: Global Game Jam, Sci-Fi series, Stackover-

flow, Fitness and Martial Arts

Experience

2016 / 09 - University of Bremen

Fullstack Javascript Engineer

- Invent a realtime classroom management using Meteor and React
- Design software architecture and leading development

2014 - 2016 - We4IT GmbH Bremen

IT Consultant for IBM XPages and Notes Domino

- ▶ Realize projects in XPages and We4IT Aveedo, monitor project status, conduct reports
- Integrated Camunda BPMN engine and BPMN.IO modeler in We4IT Aveedo

2012 - 2014 - University of Bremen

Scientific Employee / Software Development

- Invented a flexible assessment framework, targeting industrial trainees
- **)** Supervised software development lifecycle, Recruited team members

2011 / 11 - Getog Consulting

Project Management Simulation Training

- ▶ Performed a two-day project simulation from management perspective
- ➤ Topics included customer contracts, change management, controlling, operational tasks

2010 - 2011 - otulea uni-bremen de

Student Assistant / Programmer

- ▶ Realized an online diagnosis platform for workforce literacy development (Flex)
- Modeled software design, implemented various prototypes, conducted usability tests